あと　みっか　したら→
「おしょうがつ」でございますよ
みなさん。
うわ～　すばらしい　「こうよう」！
きれい～
さい「こうよう」（さいこうよ）！
みなさん　よいおとしを
おむかえくださいませ。
それでは　みなさん　ワンダホー！
回想
[無線]（エニグマ）やれやれ…。
今回のマスターブレインも　また→
It's unbelievable...
Yet another Master Brain failed to defeat Daimon Kaito.
大門カイトを倒せなかったよ。
（レイツェル）一体　何やってるの？
What the heck is wrong with them?!
[無線]すまないねえ
僕が　ふがいないばっかりに。→
My apologies! I only have my own shortcomings to blame...
何か　いい作戦は　ないものか…。
Would you happen to have any good tricks up your sleeve?
最近　ルークが
ピタゴラスの遺跡を探ってるって話→
Didn't you mention that Rook has been
sniffing around the Pythagoras Ruins lately?
してたわよね？
[無線]ああ。　それが何か？
That's correct. What of it?
I just came up with something sweet.
（レイツェル）いい事　思いついちゃった。
心の声
（レイツェル）大門カイトたちも
そろそろ　この旅の意味に→
By now, Daimon Kaito and his friends should have a good idea what this journey's really about.
気付いているはず。→
もう　エニグマなんかに
任せておけないわ。→
I can't rely on Enigma anymore!
私の手で　直接　あいつらを…。
I'll have to deal with them with my own two hands!
（真方ジン）
相変わらず　なまぬるいパズルだ。→
You've made yet another halfhearted puzzle.
この程度のパズルで　本当に
大門カイトを倒せるとでも？→
Do you truly believe you can defeat Daimon Kaito with such a pathetic puzzle?
いいか　目的のためには
手段を選ぶな。
Listen to me. Do whatever it takes to realize your goal.
やるのなら　徹底的にやれ。
If you're going to do something, do it thoroughly.
ジン？
Jin?
そろそろ　お茶にしようか。
Isn't it about time you stopped and had some tea?
え…　ええ。　そうね…。
Y-Yeah...
That sounds good.
心の声
（レイツェル）徹底的に…。
Do it thoroughly...
Cough! Cough!
（大門カイト）やっぱ
ヘルベルトの情報は罠だったか。
Sure enough, Herbert's information led us to a trap!
（キュービック・Ｇ）次に向かうべき場所の
情報はあったけど…。
But we found out where we're supposed to go next!
（井藤ノノハ）私　もう帰りたい。
（イワシミズ君）イワシミズ君も帰りたい。
I'm ready to go home!
Iwashimizu wants to go home!
All we're gonna find is another Master Brain waiting for us, right?
どうせ　待ってんの
また　マスターブレインなんでしょ？
I think... we won't be able to solve Raerae's puzzle if we quit!
（アナ・グラム）思うに…　やめたら
レイレイのパズルを解いた事にならない。
財のジンさんを
手に入れなければ→
Doesn't it mean we've lost the puzzle if we don't obtain Jin, the prize?
このパズル
僕らの負けって事になるよね。
（イワシミズ君）負けだね。
それは　そうだけど…。
It equals defeat.
Well, sure it does.
行こうぜ　次のパズルに。
Let's go! We're moving on to the next puzzle.
（逆之上ギャモン）これは明らかに
レイツェルの罠だ。　それでも行くのか？
That's clearly Raetsel's trap. And you still wanna go?
I don't care if it's a trap or not.
罠だろうが何だろうが
ジンに迫る手がかりを得るには→
It's the only way to find the clues that will bring me closer to Jin.
これしかねえ。
乗ってやろうじゃねえか…。
Let's play along with this game of hers.
If she's going to throw a thousand puzzles at me, then I'm going to solve every single one of them!
あいつが　１，０００のパズルで
迎え撃つなら→
俺は　そのパズルを全て解く。
他に道は　ないみたいだね。
（イワシミズ君）しかたないね。
It looks like we don't have any other options.
We must continue.
Just you wait, Raetsel!
心の声
待ってろよ　レイツェル。
必ず　お前に追いついてみせる。
I swear that I will catch up to you!
それじゃあ　ジン
私　行ってくるわ。
All right, Jin. I'm heading out now.
お留守番　頼むわね。
ああ。
Please hold down the fort, okay?
Sure.
どこにも行かないでね。　約束よ。
（ジン）分かってるよ。
Please don't go anywhere. Promise me you won't!
I know.
ごめんなさい。　私　ジンの事
振り回してばっかりで…。
I'm sorry. I keep ordering you around...
いや　僕は　一日も早く
記憶を取り戻して→
It's fine. I want to make you and Kaito happy by recovering my memories as soon as possible.
君と　カイト君を喜ばせたいんだ。
I'm the one who should be apologizing to you.
謝らなきゃいけないのは
僕の方だよ。
ジン…。
Jin...
思い出せなくて　ごめんよ　レイツェル。
I'm sorry I can't remember anything, Raetsel.
It doesn't matter if your memories never return!
記憶なんて
なくても構わない。
もし　思い出せなくても　私が
ずっと　そばにいてあげるから。
Even if they never come back, I'll always be with you.
Jin, I'm going to do a thorough job.
ジン…　私　徹底的にやる。
そう決めたの。
I've decided to go through with it.
So...
だから…→
私のお願い　もう一つだけ
聞いてくれる？
Could you do one more thing for me?
This is the next puzzle, huh?
次のパズルは　こいつか。
よっしゃ　行こうぜ！
All right! Let's go!
ストップ！
おっ!?
Stop!
I'm against this after all.
やっぱり　私　反対。
こんな危険な事
続ける意味ないよ。
There's no point in continuing with these dangerous puzzles!
ノノハ　これは…。
いくら　みんなが！
Nonoha, this is—
Even if everyone...
いくら　みんなが
パズルを解き続けられるとしても→
Even if everyone is able to continue solving puzzles, will this journey ever come to an end?
この旅　本当に終わりはあるの？
（レイツェル）安心して！
（カイト　ギャモン）あっ!?
Don't you worry!
Your journey will come to an end.
君たちの旅は終わるわ。
今日　ここでね。
It ends right here! Today!
Raetsel!
レイツェル！
Welcome! This will be your last stop.
ようこそ　旅の終着点へ。
You've finally shown yourself!
（キュービック）ついに現れたね。
（イワシミズ君）現れたね。
You've shown yourself!
What do you mean by "last stop"?
終着点って　どういう意味!?
I'm going to show you the extent of my determination!
見せてあげるわ　私の覚悟を。
（指を鳴らす音）
（一同）あっ。
ジン！
Jin!
「やあ　久しぶりだね　カイト君」。
Hey! It's been a while, hasn't it, Kaito?
だまされんな　カイト。
偽もんの真逆ジンかもしんねえぞ
Don't be duped, Kaito!
That could be the imposter, Masaka Jin.
I think... that Jinjin is eal-ray.
思うに　あのジンジンは　モノホン。
ジン　今どこに…。
Jin, where are you?!
（カイト　ギャモン）あっ!?
（アナ）ジンジン　消えちゃった。
Jinjin vanished.
ジンは　今
このピラミッドの中にいるわ。→
Jin is currently inside of this pyramid.
私のパズルを解放できれば
財のジンは君のもの。
If you can free my puzzle, the prize, Jin, is yours for the taking.
But if you fail, you'll never see Jin again.
できなければ　君は　もう二度と
ジンには会えないわ。
Let's get started!
始めるわよ。
ジンを賭けた　私と君のパズルを！
This is a puzzle between you and me with Jin on the line!
（レイツェル）ルールは簡単よ。
この迷路を抜けて→
The rules are simple!
Make your way through this maze and reach the goal in the center alive!
中心にある　ゴールまで
生きて　たどりつきなさい。
This maze? But I don't see a maze anywhere!
（キュービック）
「この迷路」って…　どこにも
迷路なんてないじゃないか。
（アナ）道が出来てる。
Now there are pathways!
（ギャモン）全体が見えない状態で
ゴールを目指せってか!?
You want us to head for the goal when we can't see the whole thing?
壁の上には　電流が流れてるわ。
There are electric currents flowing across the top of the walls.
登って　全体を見渡そうとしても
無駄よ。→
So don't think you can climb to the top and study the maze.
Do your very best to try to reach the prize, Jin!
財のジンを目指して
せいぜい頑張る事ね。
くっ…。　てめえ！　こんな事して
どうかしてんじゃねえか!?
You little shit! Have you completely lost your mind?!
He's right!
そうよ！　ジンさんは
あなたにとって→
Don't you care for Jin more than anyone else in the world?!
一番　大切な人じゃなかったの!?
Jin told me that I lack something!
ジンは言ってたわ！
私には何かが欠けてるって。
きっと　それは覚悟だったのよ！
I'm sure that must have been determination!
覚悟って…。　こんなのが
あなたの覚悟だっていうの？
Determination?
And this is what you call "determination"?
目的のためには
手段を選ばないわ。→
I'll do whatever it takes to realize my goal!
I'd be willing to sell my soul to the devil if it'd help me defeat you!
君たちを倒すためなら→
悪魔にだって
魂を売り渡してやる！
ジンは　俺が
必ず取り戻してみせる！
I swear that I will get Jin back.
パズルタイムの始まりだ！
It's puzzle time!
The philosopher Pythagoras had a puzzle here?
（ルーク・盤城・クロスフィールド）こんな所に
賢者ピタゴラスのパズルが…。
（ビショップ）いまだ
財が発見されていないので→
The prize has yet to be found, so people
thought he abandoned it before completion.
作りかけで放棄されたと
考えられていましたが→
ようやく　ここにある事が
分かりました。
But I recently learned that this is where he put it.
神のパズルの真実を記したと
言われる　ピタゴラス文書。→
The truth behind the Divine Puzzle is said to be recorded in the Pythagoras Document.
いよいよだね…。
We've finally found it!
申し訳ございません　ルーク様。
私では　お力になれず…。
I am terribly sorry, Sir Rook.
I will not be able to assist you.
いいんだ。　今は待とうじゃないか。
That's fine.
For now, let's wait for him to get here.
彼の到着を…。
心の声
（レイツェル）私は甘かった。
なまぬるかったのよ。→
I was being naïve. I was way too soft.
心のどこかで　大門カイトに
哀れみをかけていた。→
Somewhere in my heart, a part of me was showing mercy to Daimon Kaito.
でも　もう迷ったりはしない。→
But I'm done hesitating!
私とジンの旅も　これで終わるわ。
そして　彼らの旅も…。
After this, my journey with Jin will come to an end.
The same goes for them.
Cubie, where'd Iwarin go?
（アナ）キュー太郎　イワリンは？
He said that he hates dank places.
ジメジメした所　嫌いなんだって。
カイト　最初の分岐だよ。
どっちに行く？
Kaito, this is our first fork. Which way should we go?
ここは　左手式で行く。
Let's stick with the left-hand rule.
えっ…　それって　壁に触りながら
ゴールを目指すって方法だよね。
Huh? Isn't that when you head for the goal while touching the wall?
でも　それじゃ解けない
迷路があるって…。
ほえ！
But aren't there some mazes where that doesn't work?
Really?
ああ　確かに。
Yeah, you're right.
When the starting point is on the outside and the goal is in the center, hugging the wall won't always work.
スタートが外側で
ゴールが内側にある場合→
壁伝いでも
ゴールに　たどりつけない事がある。
だから　それも考えに入れながら
壁伝いに進み…。
So we'll keep that in mind while hugging the wall.
行き止まりを見つけたら
その通路はパスする。
If we find a dead end, we'll skip that passageway.
（アナ）次は　お箸　持つ方！
Follow your chopsticks hand next!
あれっ　左手式じゃなかったの？
こっちは？
Huh? Weren't we following the left-hand rule?
Not going left?
こっちは　行き止まりなんだよ。
えっ　どうして？
Going left leads to a dead end.
Huh? What makes you say that?
これまで　たどってきたルートを
思い出して。→
Think back on the routes we've taken thus far.
この先が　行き止まりだって事は
行かなくても分かるんだよ。
You don't need to go left to know it's a dead end.
なるほど！
I get it!
こうやって　臨機応変に
道を選んでいくのが→
The best way to solve this maze is to play it by ear as you go.
この迷路の攻略法だよ。
ヘッ！　大層な前振りの割には
楽勝じゃねえか。
For such a grand prelude, this is stinking easy!
Yeah! This isn't the least bit challenging, is it?
うん。　全然　大した事ないね。
心の声
でも　何かが　おかしい。→
But something feels off.
このパズルからは
何も　声が聞こえねえ。
I can't hear any voices coming from this puzzle.
（ビショップ）
ようこそ　お越し下さいました。→
Thank you for joining us,
Mr. Pinochle and Mr. Freecell.
ピノクルさん　フリーセルさん。
呼び出してしまって
すまないね。
I'm sorry to have asked you to come out here.
No, it's fine.
（フリーセル）いや　いいんだ。
早速だけど
賢者ピタゴラスのパズルっていうのは？
Let's skip the formalities.
Where is the philosopher Pythagoras' puzzle?
こちらです。
（フリーセル）これが…。
This is it.
Really?
The prize sealed inside is the Pythagoras Texts.
（ビショップ）封じられし財は
ピタゴラス文書。→
賢者ピタゴラスによって
神のパズルの真実が記されたと→
It is believed that the philosopher Pythagoras recorded the truth pertaining to the Divine Puzzle in this document.
考えられる書物です。
そこには　必ず→
I am confident that it contains the hints we need to help Jin recover his memories!
ジンの記憶を取り戻す
手がかりが隠されているはずだ。
We would like to request your assistance
この財を手に入れるため→
in order to obtain this prize, Mr. Freecell.
フリーセルさんに
お力を貸して頂きたいのです。
でも…　できるかな？　僕に。
But I wonder if I'm up to the task...
できるさ。　ファイ・ブレインの子供たちの
一人である君になら。
I'm sure you are!
You're a child of the Phi Brain, so I'm sure you can.
納得できないよ　僕は。
I'm not so sure about that.
フリーセルは　しばらく
パズルから離れていたんだ。
Freecell had stopped solving puzzles for a while.
いくら　ファイ・ブレインの子供たち
だからって…。
Being a child of the Phi Brain doesn't compensate for that!
ルーク君１人じゃ駄目なのかい？
Rook, can't you handle this on your own?
このパズルの解放には
必要不可欠なのです。
His assistance is essential if we are to free this puzzle.
ファイ・ブレインの子供たち
２人の協力が。
Two children of the Phi Brain must work together to release it.
だけど…。
ありがとう　ピノクル。
But!
Thank you, Pinochle.
でも　僕は　やるよ。
But I'm doing this.
フリーセル…。
Freecell...
僕は探していたんだ。
I've been searching for something that I could do to help Kaito.
カイトのために　できる事を…。
Let's work together to solve this puzzle, Freecell!
力を合わせ
共にパズルを解こう　フリーセル君。
ありがとう　ルーク君。
Thank you, Rook.
どうしたの？　カイト。
What's wrong, Kaito?
何か　おかしい。
何かって？
Something's off.
Like what?
変だと思わねえか？
このパズル　底が浅すぎる。
Don't you think it's strange?
This puzzle is way too shallow.
Huh? It's shallow?
Yeah, for something meant to crush us,
she's got the level cranked way too low!
ほえ～　底？
確かに　俺たちを
ガチに潰しにきたパズルにしちゃ→
レベルが低すぎるぜ。
レイツェルのやつ
何たくらんでやがんだ？
What the hell does Raetsel have up her sleeve?
まさか　こっちの動きを読んで…。
Did she predict how we'd move?
俺たちは　あいつの読みどおりに
動いてるって事か？
Does that mean we're doing exactly what she expected?
だったら　あえて
別のルートを確かめてやる！
In that case, let's check out some of the other routes!
えっ…　ちょっと　カイト
どこ行くの!?
Hey, Kaito! Where are you going?!
That sounds good to me!
その考え　俺も乗った！
ギャモン君まで…。
Not you too, Gammon!
Now what do we have here?!
さあ　一体　何がある？
ハァ。
どわっ!?　ふっ　だっ　だっ　だっ
だっ　ほっ　はっ　てっ…。
大丈夫？　カイト。
うっ…　ああ。
Are you okay, Kaito?
Yeah.
（レイツェル）何　ぐずぐずしてんのよ。
What's taking you so long?
君　ほんとに
ジンを取り戻す気あるの？
Are you even serious about wanting to get Jin back?
結局　ベタなルートを
行くしかねえって事か。
In the end, it looks like we're stuck taking the obvious route.
本当に　それでいいのかな？
I wonder if that's really the right thing to do.
思うに…
レイレイ　何か隠してる。
I think... Raerae is hiding something.
やっぱりだ。
全然　引っ掛かりが　ねえ。
I knew it!
There aren't any traps!
こんな単純なパズル…　俺には　とても
レイツェルが本気だとは思えねえ。
I sincerely doubt Raetsel poured her heart into such an easy puzzle.
もしかして　レイツェルは
解いてほしがってるのかも。
Maybe Raetsel actually wants us to solve it.
覚悟だなんて言ってたけど→
Despite what she said about her determination,
maybe deep down she wants to bring this to an end.
ほんとは　もう　こんな事
おしまいにしたいんじゃないかな。
Maybe she wants to give Jin back and make up with you, Kaito.
ジンさんを返して
カイトと仲直りしたいのかも。
このパズルには
レイツェルの　そんな気持ちが→
Do you think this puzzle is expressing Raetsel's inner feelings?
表れてるんじゃないかな。
ケッ！　あいつが　そんな
いい子ちゃんだと思うか？
Heh! Do you seriously think she's that sweet?
心の声
分からねえ。　分からねえが
もし　仮に　そうだとしても→
I don't know.
I don't know, but even assuming that's true, what gives?
一体　何なんだ？
この　ザワザワした嫌な感じは…。
What's with this ominous feeling nagging at me?
あ…。
あれが　ゴールだ。
That's the goal.
結局　何もなかったな。
In the end, we made it here safe and sound.
これが本当に　あいつの…
レイツェルの覚悟のパズルなのか？
Is this really the puzzle she...
that Raetsel made to show her determination?
心の声
ここまで来たら　進むしかねえ！
Now that I've come this far, I have to keep going!
ジンさんは　この中かな？
Do you think Jin is in there?
ふっ！　くっ…。
おい　開かねえぞ。
Hey! It wont budge!
パズルは解放した！
約束どおり　ジンを返せ！
We freed the puzzle!
Now keep your end of the deal and give Jin back!
分かったわ。　ジンは返すわよ。
Fine. I'll return Jin.
でも…　大門カイト！
But Daimon Kaito, are you prepared to accept the truth about Jin?
君に　ジンの真実を受け入れる
覚悟はあるのかしら？→
記憶を取り戻し
パズルを憎むようになった…。→
Upon regaining his memories, he could start to hate puzzles.
そんなジンを　君は
笑顔で迎えられるっていうの？
Could you welcome Jin with a smile if he hated them?
どうなのよ？
Let's hear it!
ま…　確かに
一理あるかもしれねえな。
Well, she may have a point.
ギャモン君？
Gammon?
ジンの記憶には
何が隠されているか→
We seriously have no idea what lies hidden within Jin's memories.
マジで分かったもんじゃねえぜ。
これまでだって
さんざん見てきたじゃねえか。
But we've had some nasty shit thrown in our faces!
回想
全てのパズラーを　せん滅する。
真方ジンとの盟約に従って…。
To annihilate all puzzlers
as per my covenant with Makata Jin.
回想
（ルーク）「これらが真方ジンによって
作られた可能性が→
It has come to my attention that it is highly likely that Makata Jin built them.
高いと分かった」。
思うに…　真実は痛い。
I think... that the truth hurts.
もし　記憶が戻ったジンが
マジで→
When Jin gets his memories back, what if he really does want to annihilate all puzzlers?
全てのパズラーを滅ぼそうとする
ようなやつだったら…。→
Just thinking about it makes my skin crawl!
考えただけでも　ゾッとするぜ。
そうかもしれないけど…。
That may be true...
See! You have no right to receive Jin!
ほ～ら　やっぱり　君たちに
ジンを迎える資格なんてない。
ジンは　このまま
私といるのが一番幸せなのよ。
It would be best for Jin if he stayed with me.
Yeah, you might be right.
ああ…　かもしれねえな。
だが　カイトは　そうは思っちゃいない
みてえだぜ。
But it looks like Kaito doesn't feel that way!
俺は　真実から目を背けねえ。
I won't turn away from the truth!
I'll take any pain that life throws at me!
どんな痛みだって
受け止めてやるぜ！
（レイツェル）へえ～。
記憶を取り戻したジンが→
Oh? So you wouldn't care if Jin rejected you once he regained his memories?
君を拒絶したとしても
構わないっていうの？→
捨てられてもいいっていうの？
You wouldn't care if he abandoned you?
ああ　構わねえ。
Yeah, I wouldn't care.
それが
ジンの教えてくれた事だからだ！
Because I'd be following what Jin taught me!
Do you ever think of them? Of your mother and father?
回想
（ジン）思い出すのか？
父さんと母さんの事を。
忘れられるはずないよ。
I could never forget them!
（ジン）忘れる必要なんて　ない。
えっ？
And you don't need to.
目を背けても　過去は
なかった事にはならない。→
Even if you look away, you can't undo the past.
真実から　目をそらすな。→
Don't turn away from the truth.
目をそらせば　パズルは
永遠に解けないままだ。
If you look away, you will never be able to solve your puzzle.
人生という名の　パズルもな。
The puzzle known as "life."
真実から　目をそらすな…。
"Don't turn away from the truth."
それを教えてくれたのは
他でもない　ジンなんだ！
The one who taught me that was none other than Jin!
目を背けても　過去は
なかった事にはならねえ！
Even if I look away, I can't undo the past!
だから　俺は　パズルを解く！
そして　真実をつかんでみせる！
That's why I solve puzzles!
And I will grab hold of the truth!
Now return Jin! Give Jin back to me!
さあ　ジンを…　ジンを返せ！
フッ　ほんと勝てないわね
君には…。
There really is no beating you.
I'll keep my promise. You can have Jin.
約束は守るわ。
ジンは君たちのものよ。
He's in here!
いたぞ！
ジン！
Jin!
あっ!?　お前　まさか…。
Aren't you... No way!
真逆ジン！
（真逆ジン）あ…　あぁ…。
You're Masaka Jin!
あぁ…　あ…。
何で　偽者のお前が
いんだよ!?
What the heck is an imposter like you doing in here?!
Where's the Jin who talked to us earlier?!
さっき　しゃべったジンは
どこだ!?
し…　知らない。　私は　ただ
ここにいろって言われたから…。
I-I-I-I don't know! She just told me to stay in here!
（モニター・レイツェル）
「フッ　フフフフ…　アハハハ！　アーハハハハ…」。
どういう事だ!?　レイツェル！
What's this all about, Raetsel?!
「約束どおり　ジンは返したわ」。
（ギャモン）てめえ！
Just as promised, I've returned Jin.
Bitch!
I never said that it would be Makata Jin.
「真方ジンなんて
ひと言も言ってないわよ。→
私が　そんな簡単に
本物のジンを渡すと→
Did you honestly think I'd be that quick to hand over the real Jin?
本気で思ってたわけ？→
You should know better than that.
そんなわけないじゃない」。
回想
（レイツェル）カイトと通信をつなぐけど
どこにいるかは言わないで。
I'm going to transmit this to Kaito,
but please don't tell him where you are.
なぜだい？
Why not?
Please don't.
お願い。
「残念だったわね。　そして
まだ　私のパズルは終わってないわ」。
Nice try. My puzzle isn't over yet either.
（ギャモン）な…。
何!?
Wha?!
What?!
あぁ…。
出口が！
The exit!
Didn't I warn you?
「言ったでしょ？
私　目的のためには→
I'll do whatever it takes to realize my goal!
手段を選ばないって。→
さあ　第２ステージの始まりよ！→
Now then, it's time for the second stage to begin!
ただし　ソルヴァーは君じゃないわ」。
何だと!?
However, you won't be the Solver.
Say what?!
気を付けてね　フリーセル。
行ってらっしゃいませ　ルーク様。
Please be careful, Freecell.
Take care, Sir Rook.
そろそろ　教えてくれないか？
Don't you think it's about time you told me?
何だい？
Told you what?
ファイ・ブレインの子供たちが
２人必要って→
What exactly did he mean when he said that it would take two children of the Phi Brain?
一体どういう事？
それは…。
Well...
（モニター・レイツェル）
「ようこそ　私のパズルへ」。
Welcome to my puzzle!
（モニター・レイツェル）「賢者ピタゴラスだか
何だか知らないけど→
I don't care at all about that philosopher Pythagoras.
I've taken the liberty to tweak this puzzle!
このパズル
私が細工させてもらったわ」。
Let's see the extent of this kitten's "determination."
さて　見せてもらおうか。→
子猫の覚悟とやらを…。
（フリーセル）カイト！
Kaito?!
さあ！　大門カイトを財とした
パズルタイムの始まりよ！
Okay! With Daimon Kaito as your prize, it's puzzle time!
Preview
I shall rescue Kaito and the others.
What's your plan of action, Principal?